thefinanceadvocate.com 2017-12-27

# The Finance Advocate

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how we (“A4D”) collect and use the information you provide when you visit our website at thefinanceadvocate.com (along with all subdomains, collectively, the “Site”). This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. 

We never knowingly collect or maintain information from those we know are under 18 years old, and no part of our Site is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 18 years old. Visitors younger than 18 years of age may not use the Site.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine the Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. This information would include a standardized list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: 

A4D, Inc.   
Attn: A4D Legal Department – The Finance Advocate   
6965 El Camino Real, Suite 105-441  
Carlsbad, CA, 92009  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  

### Types of Information Collected

The only information we collect from you is anonymous data. We automatically track and collect the following types of information: 1) IP addresses; 2) domain servers; 3) types of computers accessing the Site; and 4) types of web browsers used to access the Site. Third party service providers also collect information from you when you use our site, including information about your use of our Site (for example, pages displayed and items clicked) and information that that is useful for displaying customized advertising to you.

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. A4D collects information through cookies and web beacons about your web browsing activities such as the address of the page you are visiting, the address of the referrer page you previously visited, the time you are viewing the page, your browsing environment and your display settings. We place a cookie on your computer to: analyze web traffic patterns on the Site and other non-A4D websites; understand how you use and interact with the Site; optimize your experience on our Site; obtain anonymous individual or aggregate auditing, research, modeling and reporting information; provide you relevant advertising and content; and properly manage our Site.

Please note that cookies and web beacons are also placed by third party service providers who perform some of these functions for us. Other companies’ use of their cookies and web beacons is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. If you are concerned about cookies, most browsers permit individuals to decline cookies. A user refusing cookies can still fully navigate our Site. Similarly, code on our site will cause your browser to communicate with our 3rd-party service providers’ computers to help us analyze your use of our Site.

### Uses of Information Collected

We use your Personal Information to understand your use of our Site, to improve the site, and to cause advertisements that might be of interest to you to display when you view our Site and other websites. We do this, in part, by sharing your Personal Information with 3rd party service providers (including Google) that help us understand how you use our Site and ways in which we can improve our Site.

### Sharing and Transferring Personal Information.

If you are residing outside the United States, by using this Site, you acknowledge that the processing of your Personal Information may involve the transfer of such Personal Information from within or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) to countries within or outside the EEA whose data protection regulation may not be as stringent as that within the European Union. 

### Your Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information

The information we collect about you is anonymous. Thus, we do not maintain a procedure for you to confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. 

### Customizing the Ads You See

We advertise online using third party analytic software such as Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Platform integrations, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Cookies belonging to us and third parties that are placed on your computer allow us to analyze your use of our Site and to cause advertisements to be displayed to you based on your use of our Site and other websites. You will see these ads on our Site and when you visit other websites and online services. These third parties (which include Google, DoubleClick, operators of ad servers, ad networks, and related service providers) cause advertisements and links to advertisements to be displayed to you, and they will receive your IP address when this happens. These third parties use various techniques (including cookies, JavaScript, device identifiers, location data, and web beacons) to record the pages and usage patterns of you, your browser, and your device for the purpose of customizing the advertising you see and increasing its effectiveness. To opt out of the Doubleclick cookie, visit the Google advertising opt out page. To opt out of Google Analytics, visit the Google Analytics opt out page. To opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies, visit the DoubleClick opt-out page or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

### Security

The information stored on A4D’s servers and systems use industry standard security measures (such as a firewall and password protections) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under A4D’s control. Notwithstanding such measures, A4D cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed, and the Personal Information on them stolen or altered. 

### Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. If any modification is unacceptable, your only recourse is not to use our Services and the Site.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or want to contact us, please send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or write to us at: A4D, Inc., Attn: A4D Legal Department- Finance Advocate, 6965 El Camino Real No. 105-441, Carlsbad, CA 92009.

Effective Date: November 19, 2015
